Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 2011
    - Recital of Mencius Society for the Arts, May 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-05-28
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 11-0528_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 11-0528_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 11-0528_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 11-0528_3
    - Domingos Americanos, June 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-06-12
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 11-0612_1; Note on media: lecture by Manuel Jaimes, Queens Museum of Art
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 11-0612_2; Note on media: Grupo Rebolu, Queens Museum of Art
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 11-0612_3; Note on media: Diego Obregon and Grupo Chonta, Queens Museum of Art
    - Sounds of Korea: Sue Yeon Park, January 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-01-08
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: TA 11-0801_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., TA 11-0801
    - Josh Waletzky - Yiddish singing session, January 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-01-28
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 11-0128_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., ANSKYCCI 11-0128_2
    - Sounds of Immigrant New York: Haitian Music: Elizabeth McAlister presents Haitian Music from Vodou to Gospel, Rara to Hip Hop; Brooklyn Historical Society, March 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-03-03
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOINY 11-0303_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOINY 11-0303_1
    - Tantshoyz: Ukrainian East Village Restaurant, June 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-06-01
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 11-0601_2
    - An-sky, Ukrainian East Village Restaurant, June 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-06-06
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: UKRCCI 11-0601_1
    - Egg Rolls and Egg Cream Festival: Chinese Yiddish singing table, Museum at Eldridge Street, June 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-06-12
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: CHINCCI 11-0612
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., CHINCCI 11-0612
    - Haitian Prospect Park Gathering, July 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-07-24
        - 14 video files (mts): digital., CCI 11-0724
    - Heritage Sunday, August 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-08-07
        - 41 video files (mts): digital., TA20110807
    - Haitian Vodou Gathering Rockaway, Fieldwork Park, August 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-08-21
        - 15 video files (mts): digital., CCI 11-0821
        - 15 video files (mts): digital.
    - Ansky Tantshoyz Sadigursky, September 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-09-15
        - 25 video files (mts): digital., ANSKYCCI 11-0915
        - 26 video files (mts): digital., Note on media: Two Events
    - Vechornytsi, September 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-09-24
        - 32 video files (mts): digital., CCI 11-0924; Note on media: Ukr Vechornytsi Roman L
    - Mariachi Festival Met, September 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-09-24
        - 32 video files (mts): digital.
    - Ansky Romania Shulman Ment, October 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-10-10
        - 6 video files (mts): digital., ANSKYCCI 11-1010
    - Colombian Encuentro, October 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-10-22
        - 14 video files (mts): digital., CCI 11-1022
    - Ukr Marital Mayhem Concert, October 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-10-22
        - 14 video files (mts): digital., CCI 11-1022
    - Chernobyl Concert, November and December 2011
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2011-12-02, Note on folder: Chernobyl Songs Project (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Moving Images
        - 16 video files (mts): digital., 2011-11-10, Note on media: Princeton
        - 8 video files (mts): digital., 2011-12-02, Note on media: Philly
    - Kadya Project Eldridge Street, November 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-11-20
        - 8 video files (mts): digital.
    - German Goldenshteyn Center for Jewish History, November 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-11-21
        - 13 video files (mts): digital.
    - Romani Symposium Yunakov, November 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-11-22
        - 2 video files (mts): digital.
    - Shashamagam Symposium, December 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-12-07
        - 4 video files (mts): digital.
    - German Goldenshteyn Centerfor Jewish History, December 2011
      - Moving Images, 2011-12-12
        - 5 video files (mts): digital.
    - Other events, 2011
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2011, Note on folder: Traditional Colombian Music and Dance in New York (Box-folder 11/22)
        - 1 folder, 2011-01-07, Note on folder: ADAP Conference (Box-folder 11/23)
        - 1 folder, 2011-02-25, Note on folder: Radio Banduristan International (Box-folder 11/24)
        - 1 folder, 2011-04-21, Note on folder: Sounds of the Immigrant New York (Box-folder 11/26)
        - 1 folder, 2011-06-19, Note on folder: Vechornytsi (Box-folder 11/29)
        - 1 folder, 2011-11-20, Note on folder: Opre! (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Photographs
        - 1 graphic image file (jpg): digital., 2011-08-10, CCI 11-0810; Note on media: Haitian Talk Julian Carrillo
      - Moving Images
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2011-09-16, Note on media: Sadigursky
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2011-12-12, Note on media: Julian Kytasty Savradym (The Drunken Wife)
  - Events, 2012
    - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
      - 1 oversize folder, 2012, Note on media: Lincoln Center Out of Doors (Container oversize folder 1)
      - 1 folder, 2012, Note on folder: Haitian traditional singing, drumming, and dance: three part series (Box-folder 11/32)
      - 1 folder, 2012-01-08, Note on folder: World Dance Traditions (Box-folder 11/33)
      - 1 folder, 2012-03-31, Note on folder: Kilims and Constructions (Box-folder 11/34)
      - 1 folder, 2012-06-01, Note on folder: Sevdah Songs (Box-folder 11/35)
    - Photographs
      - 548 graphic image files (jpg): digital., 2012, COLCCI 12; Note on media: Colombia Independence Day 2012 Photos by Stephanie Black
    - Moving Images
      - 10 video files (mts): digital., 2012-01-08, Note on media: APAP Showkase Alwan
      - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2012-01-09, Note on media: Voices Images Bulgaria Lincoln Cntr
      - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2012-01-18, Note on media: Shashamagam Symposium
      - 2 video files (mts): digital., 2012-01-26, Note on media: Hilka Self Reliance Sr Cntr
      - 14 video files (mts): digital., 2012-02-11, Note on media: Tantshoyz
      - 28 video files (mts): digital., 2012-02-18, Note on media: Kilims Constructions Julian Kytasty
      - 49 video files (mts): digital., 2012-02-25, Note on media: Haitian Fieldwork
      - 24 video files (mts): digital., 2012-03-14, Note on media: Haitian Field research
      - 26 video files (mts): digital., 2012-03-15, Note on media: Haitian Lionel
      - 14 video files (mts): digital., 2012-03-31, Note on media: Ukrainian Kytasty
      - 16 video files (mts): digital., 2012-04-04, Note on media: Tantshoyz Arkady Goldenshteyn Fox Rosen
      - 22 video files (mts): digital., 2012-04-11, Note on media: Haitian Song
      - 14 video files (mts): digital., 2012-04-20, Note on media: Two Events
      - 16 video files (mts): digital., 2012-05-12, Note on media: Yiddish Women Folk
      - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2012-05-14, Note on media: Makam NY Symphny Spc
      - 17 video files (mts): digital., 2012-05-19, Note on media: Vechorytsi Harmonia
      - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), 2012-06-01, AFC 2014/044: ANSKYCCI 12-0601_1; Note on media: Sevdah Songs with Merima Ključo and Eva Salina Primack
      - 12 video files (mts): digital., 2012-06-01, HaitianCCI 12-0601; Note on media: Opening The Gates Augustin Memorial
      - 9 video files (mts): digital., 2012-06-03, HaitianCCI 12-0603; Note on media: Haitian Song
      - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2012-06-24, Note on media: Chinese Youth Ensemble East River
      - 14 video files (mts): digital., 2012-07-10, Note on media: Chinese East River Ensemble
      - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2012-07-12, Note on media: Klezmer Svigals
      - 6 video files (mts): digital., 2012-07-14, HaitianCCI 12-0714; Note on media: Haitian Dance Destine
      - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2012-07-22, Note on media: Folk Colombia En El Parque
      - 24 video files (mts): digital., 2012-08-05, Note on media: Heritage Sunday Haitian
      - 11 video files (mts): digital., 2012-10-25, Note on media: Chinese Mencius Society Recital
      - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2012-10-27, Note on media: Julian Kytasty Papa Susso Ballads
      - 42 video files (mts): digital., 2012-12-01, UKRCCI 12-1201; Note on media: UkrainianCCI Final Concert
      - 13 video files (m4v): digital., 2012-12-12, COLCCI 12-1212; Note on media: First Tertulia folk Columbia
      - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2012-12-18, UKRCCI 12-1218; Note on media: UkrainianCCI Final Concert
      - 6 video files (mts); 13 video files (m4v): digital., 2012-2013, COLCCI 12/13; Note on media: Tertulia - Taller 4
      - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2012-2014, COLCCI 12/14; Note on media: Zuleta ca. 2012-2014
  - Events, 2013
    - Colombian Talleres, April-June 2013
      - Moving Images, 2013
        - 8 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Taller 1
        - 12 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Taller 2
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Tertulia - Taller 2
        - 8 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Taller 4
        - 12 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Taller 6 Pacifico
        - 32 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Tertulia Taller 6 Pacifico
      - Moving Images, 2013-04-24
        - 13 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Taller 3
        - 10 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13-0424; Note on media: Tertulia - Taller 3
      - Moving Images, 2013-06-05 to 2013-06-08
        - 13 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13-0605; Note on media: Taller 5
        - 28 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 13; Note on media: Tertulia Taller 5
    - Haitian Rara and Dominican Gaga, October-November 2013
      - Moving Images, 2013-10-12 to 2013-11-11
        - 36 video files (mts): digital., 2013-10-12, HaitianCCI 13-1012
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2013-10-28
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2013-11-04
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2013-11-11
    - Other events, 2013
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 2013, Note on folder: Truths on Haitian Vodou (Box-folder 11/36)
      - Photographs
        - 2 graphic image files (jpg): digital., 2013-03-27, Note on media: 20130327
      - Moving Images
        - 19 video files (mts): digital., 2013, COLCCI 13; Note on media: FCEP 2
        - 25 video files (mts): digital., 2013, COLCCI 13; Note on media: FCEP - 2013
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2013-01-07, Note on media: Bessarabian Klezmer Zev Feldman Christina Crowder
        - 16 video files (mts): digital., 2013-01-11, Note on media: Alwan Maqam Fest
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2013-01-12, Note on media: Alwan Maqam Fest
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2013-01-22, Note on media: Ahmet Erdogdular Interview
        - 11 video files (mts): digital., 2013-02-24, Note on media: Palenque San Basilo Colombia
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2013-02-27, Note on media: Chinatown Sr Center Opera
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2013-03-23, HaitianCCI 13-0323; Note on media: Haitian CCI
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2013-03-23, Note on media: Haitian South Oxford Space
        - 12 video files (mts): digital., 2013-04-04, Note on media: Ottoman Erdogdular Symphony Space
        - 21 video files (mts): digital., 2013-04-09
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2013-06-15, HaitianCCI 13-0615; Note on media: Haitian CCI
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2013-06-15, Note on media: Haitian Mama Lola
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2013-07-21, Note on media: Folk Colombia En El Parque
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2013-07-28, COLCCI 13-0728; Note on media: Grupo Rebolu
        - 19 video files (mts): digital., 2013-08-04, Note on media: Korean Heritage Sunday
        - 12 video files (avi): digital., 2013-08-10, HaitianCCI 13-0810; Note on media: BwaKayIman Video 1 of 2
        - 18 video files (avi): digital., 2013-08-10, HaitianCCI 13-0810; Note on media: BwaKayIman Video 2 of 2
        - 13 video files (mts): digital., 2013-09-09, Note on media: New Yiddish Song Festival
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2013-09-16, Note on media: Sveta Kundish Interview
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2013-10-05, HaitianCCI 13-1005; Note on media: Field Interviews
        - 2 video files (mts): digital., 2013-11, Note on media: Diego Obregon Hunter College
        - 1 video file (mov): digital., 2013-2014, COLCCI 13; Note on media: Diego Obregon ca. 2013-2014
  - Events, 2014
    - Faces of Ezili, March 2014
      - Photographs, 2014-03-25
        - 3 graphic image files (tif): digital.
      - Moving Images, 2014-03-25
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., HaitianCCI 14-0325; Note on media: Haitian CCI 20140325
        - 9 video files (mts): digital.
    - Rara Panou! (Rara Our Way) with KONGO, May 2014
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2014-05-09
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 11/38)
      - Moving Images, 2014-05-09
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., HaitianCCI 14-0509; Note on media: Kongo Haitian New School
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., HaitianCCI 14-0509; Note on media: HaitianCCI Rara Panou Video
    - Verite Sou Tanbou (Truths on Haitian Vodou), May 2014
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 2014
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 11/37)
      - Moving Images, 2014-05-10
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., HaitianCCI 14-0510; Note on media: Haitian CCI 20140510
        - 5 video files (mts): digital.
    - Colombian Taller Vallenato, July 2014
      - Photographs, 2014-07-16
        - 17 graphic image files (jpg), COLCCI 14-0716; Note on media: Colombian Taller Vallenato Granados
      - Moving Images, 2014-07-16
        - 12 video files (mov); 2 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 14-0716; Note on media: Colombian Taller Vallenato Granados
        - 2 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 14-0716
    - FolkCOLOMBIA en el Parque 2014, July 2014
      - Moving Images, 2014-07-20
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 14-0720_1
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 14-0720_2
        - 1 videocassette (MiniDV; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: COLCCI 14-0720_3
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., COLCCI 14-0720_1
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., COLCCI 14-0720_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., COLCCI 14-0720_3
        - 6 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 14-0720
        - 6 video files (mp4): digital., COLCCI 14; Note on media: FCParque2014 from Catherine
        - 6 video files (mts): digital., COLCCI 14; Note on media: FCParque2014 CTMD Camera
        - 95 video files (mov): digital., COLCCI 14; Note on media: FCParque2014-Noelia Video Footage
        - 40 video files (mov): digital., COLCCI 14; Note on media: FCParque2014-Video from Kerey
      - Sound Recordings, 2014-07-20
        - 7 audio files (wav): digital., COLCCI 14; Note on media: FCParque2014-Noelia Audio
    - Other events, 2014
      - Moving Images
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2014, COLCCI 14; Note on media: Colombian Taller Riosucio, Tertulia
        - 11 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-10, Note on media: AlwanMaqamFest
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-15, Note on media: Julian Kytasty Ukrainian Bandura
        - 8 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-16, COLCCI 14-0116; Note on media: Castaneda interviews
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-19, HaitianCCI 14-0119; Note on media: Haitian CCI 20140119
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-19, Note on media: Haitian South Oxford Space
        - 2 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-21, Note on media: Julian Kytasty Ukrainian Bandura
        - 11 video files (mts): digital., 2014-01-29, Note on media: Ballads Julian Kytasty Colleen Cleveland
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2014-03-20, Note on media: Haitian 20140320
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., 2014-05-17, Note on media: Sandaara At Le Poisson Rouge
        - 7 video files (mts): digital., 2014-06-20, Note on media: Colombian Taller Andean
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2014-07-22, COLCCI 14-0722; Note on media: Colombian Taller Lumbalu Ambulancias
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2014-07-23, COLCCI 14-0723; Note on media: Colombian Taller Lumbalu
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2014-07-24, COLCCI 14-0724; Note on media: Colombian Taller Bailes Cantados
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2014-07-24, COLCCI 14-0724; Note on media: Colombian Taller Las Alegres Ambulancias
        - 1 video file (mts): digital., 2014-07-27, Note on media: Alicia Svigals
        - 9 video files (mts): digital., 2014-08-03, Note on media: Heritage Sunday Echoes Divine Persian Turkic
        - 11 video files (mts): digital., 2014-08-06, COLCCI 14-0608; Note on media: Colombian Taller Llanos Orientales Castaneda
        - 3 video files (mts): digital., 2014-09-03, Note on media: Brothers Nazaroff Eldridge Street
        - 9 video files (mts): digital., 2014-09-09, Note on media: Souren Baronian Eighth Ave Interview
        - 5 video files (mts): digital., 2014-10-26, Note on media: Nariman Asanov Crimean Tatar Interview
        - 15 video files (mts): digital., 2014-10-28, Note on media: Figelin Deborah Strauss Klezmer North German
        - 4 video files (mts): digital., 2014-10-29, Note on media: Litvakus Dmitri Slepovitch
      - Sound Recordings
        - 6 audio files (mp3): digital., 2014-05-07, Note on media: Strings Black Sea Nariman Asanov
  - Events, 2015
    - Roshel Rubinov Trio At New School, May 2015
      - Moving Images, 2015-05-06
        - 7 video files (mts): digital.
    - Stonehill Jewish Collection Launch Hotel Marseilles, May 2015
      - Moving Images, 2015-05-13
        - 4 video files (mts): digital.
    - Al Drootin Klezmer Clarinetist Interview Boston, May 2015
      - Moving Images, 2015-05-15
        - 8 video files (mts): digital.
  - Events, undated
    - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: CTMD - A World of Tradition from Around the Corner (Box-folder 11/39)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: Winter Lights Concert Series (Box-folder 11/42)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: BAC (Box-folder 20/1)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: ECMS (Box-folder 20/2)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: FR (Box-folder 20/3)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: QFF (Box-folder 20/4)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: RS (Box-folder 20/5)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: SFF (Box-folder 20/6)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: SI and SOL (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Photographs
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: Balkan Recording Orchestra (Box-folder 13/1)
      - 28 b/w prints various sizes (8x10 in. and less); most accompanied by copy negs, undated, Note on folder: Dave Tarras photographs (Box-folder 13/2)
      - 6 b/w prints various sizes (8x10 in. and less), undated, Note on folder: Greek Musicians (Box-folder 13/4)
      - 16 b/w color prints 4x6 in.; 43 color prints 4x6 in. and less, undated, Note on folder: Mariachi Estrella (Box-folder 14/1)
      - 1 folder, undated, Note on folder: Sons of Thunder (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Moving Images
      - 3 video files (mp4): digital., undated, AMNH
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Benat
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: East West Music - Spring Concert; Scholorship Student Recital - Julie Tay MC. 1
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Burkick Concert
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Zev Feldman Lecture
      - 2 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Chinese Student Concert
      - 3 video files (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Singing Sessions
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: East River Ensemble
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Pablo Mayor
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Sevdah Songs
      - 1 video file (mp4): digital., undated, Note on media: Andy Statman Show and Interview
    - Sound Recordings
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_1
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_2
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_3
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_4
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_5
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: DS_6
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: POP_11
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: POP_12
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: unidentified reel 1
      - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: unidentified reel 2
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-1
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-2
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-3
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-4
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-5
      - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., undated, AFC 2014/044: US-6
      - 1 audio file (wav): digital., undated, Note on media: LivingInAmerica_Tape#1
      - 2 audio files (mp3); 2 audio files (wav): digital., undated, Note on media: Enver Sherfedinov Crimean Tatar Early 1980s from Nariman Asanov
      - 3 audio files (mp3); 3 audio files (wav): digital., undated, Note on media: Chaim Berman
      - 2 audio files (wav): digital., undated, Note on media: Rushefsky Shulman-Ment Ternovka Sessions